米特私人影院欢迎您
安静。 开门 ， 开门。
Quiet. Open the door, open the door.
什么 ？
What?
究竟是怎么回事 ？
What in the devil?
你能站起来 ， 并带我们到现金抽屉 ， 夫人 ？
Can you please stand up and take us to the cash drawer, ma'am?
我不会。
I will not.
我们没有问。
We ain't asking.
是没有钱的抽屉。
There's no money in the drawers yet.
它在我的代码。
It's in the safe and i ain't got the code.
证明这一点。 抽屉 ！
Prove it. Drawer!
在这里。
Here.
打开抽屉。
Open the drawer.
我需要钥匙。 键。
I need the keys. Keys.
退后一步。
Step back.
狗屎。 该死 ！
Shit. Damn it!
你们都在这个新的 ， 我猜。
Y'all are new at this, I'm guessing.
钱在哪里 ？
Where's the money?
我告诉你 ， 它是安全的。
I told you, it's in the safe.
嗯 ， 谁有代码?
Well, who has the code?
Mr. clauson 。
Mr. clauson.
他很快就会来这里 ， 我建议大家不要来。
He'll be here soon and I suggest you fellas don't be.
你现在是个笨蛋。
All you're guilty of right now is being stupid.
让一切都有。
Just leave and that's all it'll be.
告诉我我很笨。
Tell me I'm stupid again.
什么时间先生 clauson 过来 ？ ” 夫人 ， 看着我。
What time does Mr. clauson get here? Ma'am, look at me.
什么时间先生 clauson 得到么 ？
What time does Mr. clauson get here, huh?
每天早上 8 ： 30 。
8:30 every morning.
我们步行。
We're walking.
席地而坐。
And sit.
你想去哪里 ？
Where do you think you're going?
坐在地板上 ！
Sit on the floor!
你很愚蠢。
You're stupid.
这不是关于你 ， 宝贝。
This ain't about you, darling.
艾西 ， 你没事吧 ？
Elsie, you all right?
早晨好。
Good morning.
你没有打他。
You didn't have to hit him.
喔 ！
Whoo!
慢下来。 我没有超速。
Slow down. I ain't speeding.
瞧 ， 弟弟 ， 一个没有烦恼的世界。
See, little brother, not a worry in the world.
这个规划和做是两回事。
Planning this and doing it is two different things.
也许我们应该提前赶到那儿了 ， 他以光怪陆离。
Maybe we should get there ahead, get up to olney.
早起的鸟儿有虫吃。
Early bird gets the worm.
- 慢下来。 - 我不会超速。
- Slow down. - I ain't speeding.
我发现这些硬币了。
I found these coins in the barn.
上帝知道多久他们已经坐在那里。
Lord knows how long they've been sitting there.
我为生的犯人的饮食 ，
I've been living off an inmate's diet,
万幸 ， 这些硬币
and had all these coins
坐在下面的饲料袋。
sitting right underneath a bunch of feed sacks.
1953 年写的。
This one says 1953.
1953 年 ？
1953?
我认为这些是收藏家的物品。
I wonder if any of these is collector's items.
你可以坐在这里的。
You could be sitting on a fortune here.
我希望如此。
I hope so.
早安 ， 各位。 拉开抽屉 ！
Good morning, folks. Open the drawer!
打开抽屉拿下来 ！
Open the motherfucking drawer!
1 、 5 、 10s 、 20s 、数百无 ， 没有。
Ones, fives, 10s, 20s, no hundreds, no bundles.
你们抢劫了银行吗 ？
You boys robbing the bank?
闭嘴。
Shut up.
把你的手放在柜台上。 在柜台上。
Put your hands on the counter. On the counter.
是的 ， 先生。 就这样 ， 来吧。
Yes, sir. That's it, come on.
别傻了 ， 你们根本就不是墨西哥人。
That's crazy, y'all ain't even Mexicans.
嗯 ， 嗯。
Uh-uh, uh-uh.
没有束。 只是闲钱。
No bundles. Just loose cash.
好吧。
Okay.
你应该为自己感到羞耻。
You ought to be ashamed of yourselves.
双手在那里我可以看到他们 ！
Hands on the counter where I can see them!
是的 ， 先生。
Yes, sir.
你对你有枪吗 ， 老头 ？
You got a gun on you, old man?
你说得对我带枪。
You're damn right i got a gun on me.
你要拿枪 ？ 是啊。
Are you gonna get his gun? Yeah.
跟不上的情况 ， 好吗 ？
Keep up with the circumstances, okay?
嗯 ， 我知道了。
Yeah, I got it.
所以你们要拿走我的枪 ？
So y'all gonna steal my gun, too?
我有我自己的枪。
I have my own gun.
我们不是偷你东西。 我们从偷银行。
We ain't stealing from you. We're stealing from the bank.
非常感谢。
Much obliged.
我们走吧 ！
Let's go!
我们很抱歉 ， 各位。
We're sorry about this, folks.
脏 ， 臭婊子养的。
Dirty, rotten sons of bitches.
操你 ， 老头 ！
Fuck you, old man!
走 ， 跑 ， 跑 ！
Go, run, go!
把枪放在柜台上。
Put the gun on the counter.
你想害死我们吗 ？
You trying to get us killed?
我不是偷的是一些老人。
I ain't stealing from some old man.
我们从一个地方 ， 就是它。
We're stealing from one place, that's it.
你是一个可怜的罪犯。
You're turning out to be a poor-ass criminal.
哦 ， 你他妈的。
Oh, fuck you.
喔 ！
Whoo!
早起的鸟儿有虫吃 ， 看什么 ？
See what the early bird gets?
也许我们应该打那个分支在杰顿 ？
Maybe we should hit that branch in jayton?
不 ， 我们不是。 我们这些银行
No, we ain't. We hit those banks
首先在该死的清晨 ， 当他们空。
first thing in the fucking morning, when they're empty.
当清空时 ， 该死的 ！
When they're empty, god damn it.
好吧。
All right.
这是我最后一次在继续拍摄。
It's the last time i care to be shot at.
我们得聪明点。 离我们不远了。
We got to be smart. We're a ways from being finished.
妈 ， 我能做到这一切。
Shit, I can do this all week.
我们要。
We're gonna.
我们等着笔于卡曼契人 ， 小弟
We're like the comanches, little brother,
我们请奇袭
raiding where we please
在德克萨斯州捕猎我们的影子。
with the whole of Texas hunting our shadow.
《平原。
Lord of the plains.
噢 ， 噢 ， 噢 ， 噢 ， 噢 ！
Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh!
把手拿开。 滚开 ！
Hands off. Fuck off!
你听过这些抢劫银行 ？
You hear about these bank robberies?
为什么你总是穿得像我吗 ？
Why are you always dressed like me?
这是我们的制服。
This is our uniform.
我们都不均匀。
We ain't got no uniform.
你可以穿上任何颜色的衬衫。
You can wear whatever color shirt you choose.
你选择了我。
You just keep choosing mine.
游侠 REG 说白色、蓝色或褐色衬衫。
Ranger regs say white, blue, or tan dress shirts.
理所当然的
Stands to reason every once in a while
我们要穿得一模一样。
we're gonna be dressed the same.
嗯 ， 你知道他们怎么说 ， 阿尔伯特。
Well, you know what they say about imitation, Alberto.
你想听到这些银行抢劫案
You wanna hear about these bank robberies,
或者你只是坐在那里 ， 让老年痴呆症。
or you just sit there and let Alzheimer's run its course.
他们在哪里 ？
Where are they at?
德克萨斯州米德兰。 弓箭手和城市中分支的分支在奥尔尼。
Texas Midlands. Branch in Archer city and the branch in olney.
想协助联邦调查局的 ？
FBI want an assist?
中部没有任何分支机构。
Midlands ain't got any branches outside Texas.
另外 ， 他们刚刚打了几个抽屉。
Plus, they're just hitting the drawers for a few thousand.
FBI 不想要它。
FBI don't want it.
你可以找点儿乐子
You may get to have some fun
在他们把你们关到摇椅。
before they send you off to the rocking chair yet.
我需要你冷静。
I need you sober.
谁喝醉了的啤酒吗 ？
Who the hell gets drunk off a beer?
地方看起来像狗屎。
Place looks like shit.
你还有什么别的你想说什么?
You got anything else you wanna say?
没有一个像样的牛排
There's not a decent steak
在大部分的他们 ， 对不起狗娘养的。
in the whole lot of them, the sorry sons of bitches.
是啊 ， 当你在监狱里忙 ，
Yeah, well, while you were busy in jail,
我在忙着照顾妈妈 ，
I was busy looking after mama,
所以你可以去他妈的自己。
so you can go fuck yourself.
她是在床上吗 ？
Was she in that bed a while?
3 个月。
Three months.
最后是很大的。
The end there was pretty rough.
我可以帮忙的时候 ， 她问。
I could've helped out a little if she asked.
我可以给他们瘦牛。
I could've fed them skinny cows.
她说 ： “我们没有喂它们。
We had nothing to feed them.
嗯 ， 我可以帮助清理房子。
Well, I could've helped clean up the house a bit.
我从来没想过你了房屋清洁。
I never took you for the go-to guy for house cleaning.
没有。 只是抢劫银行。
No. Just robbing banks.
是啊。
Yeah.
他妈的她。 她从没想过跟我没有关系。
Fuck her. She never wanted nothing to do with me anyway.
她会留下吗 ？
She leave a will?
是啊。
Yeah.
我在这 ？
Am I in it?
将不重要的。
The will don't matter.
她离开了我的一切。
She left everything to me.
这一切都由星期五我的孩子们。
By Friday it all goes to my boys.
她不想。
She didn't mean nothing by it.
她肯定有这个意思。
She damn sure meant it.
她一直恨我了。
She always hated me for standing up to him.
我们都受到了惩罚。
We all got punished.
你从不了解战斗后进行殴打。
You never understood that fighting back makes the beating last longer.
不 ， 我理解。
No, I understood.
这就是为什么我停止打斗和枪杀那婊子养的。
That's why I stopped fighting and shot that son of a bitch.
嘿 ， 怎么了 ？
Hey, what's going on?
有人今天上午抢劫了银行。
Somebody robbed the bank this morning.
做什么 ？
Do what?
如果你看到有多少 ， 就给我打电话。
If you see anyone looking a little sideways, give me a call.
侧向不想见我。
Sideways don't wanna meet me.
由于错误的一小段绳子。
Find itself on the wrong end of a short rope.
哦 ， 好吧 ， 事情也就简单为大家但你。
Oh, well, that would simplify things for everyone but you.
也许 ， 如果你能找到的树。
Maybe, if you can find the tree.
上帝 ， 我爱得克萨斯西部。
God, i love west Texas.
游侠 ？ 嗨 ， 大家好。
Ranger? Hi there.
不是抢劫
Wasn't much of a robbery,
只受到 7000 美元。
got off with just under $7,000.
把抽屉的钱 ， 并在 20s ，
Took the drawer money, 20s and under,
仅松散。
only loose bills.
墨水包没有 ？ 不是的。
No ink pack? Nope.
智能。 好聪明。
Smart. That was smart.
我们可以去看视频吗 ？
Can we get a look at the video?
让我介绍你的银行经理 clauson 。
Let me introduce you to the bank manager, Mr. clauson.
这里是护林员。
This here is ranger Hamilton.
游侠。 爵士。
Ranger. Sir.
我们能看看监控录像吗 ？
Can we get a look at the surveillance video?
我们有摄像头 ，
We got cameras,
但我们在数字交换系统
but they're switching us over to a digital system
馈送到该计算机。
that feeds into the computer.
这些新的摄像机不以我们的 VCR 。
These new cameras don't hook to our vcrs.
呼吁年轻县警长。
Call over the young county sheriffs.
问他们是否认为他们的相机钩
Ask them if they thought to hook their cameras
某种记录设备。
to some sort of recording device.
武装 ？ 是的 ， 先生。 手枪。
Armed? Yes, sir. Pistols.
哦。
Oh.
脸上吗 ？
Faces covered?
滑雪面罩、运动衫、宽松的裤子..
Ski masks, sweatshirts, baggy pants...
嗯嗯。 他们就像暴徒在达拉斯。
Uh-huh. Like them thugs in Dallas.
修改者借机 ， 也许 ？
Tweakers maybe?
也许。
Maybe.
早在上午的修改者借机。
A little early in the morning for tweakers.
修改者借机不睡觉。 他们只是微调。
Tweakers don't sleep. They just tweak.
他们抢劫药店和停放汽车 ， 不是银行。
They rob drug stores and parked cars, not banks.
我能看一下里面吗 ？
Can I take a look inside?
是的 ， 先生。
Yes, sir.
是啊 ， 我拿着 ， 玛格丽特。
Yeah, I'm here, Margaret.
所以你的小苹果大鼻子应该 ， 嗯 ？
So they bopped you on the schnozzola, huh?
是的 ， 先生。
Yes, sir.
不是很好。
Not very nice.
我认得它们的面孔。
I know their faces was covered,
但你能告诉他们吗 ？
but could you tell their race?
黑色、白色 ？
Black, white?
他们的皮肤和灵魂吗 ？
Their skin or their souls?
我们让他们的灵魂。
Let's leave their souls out of this for now.
白色。
White.
这附近的某个地方 ， 我猜 ，
From around here somewhere is my guess,
你知道 ， 从他们的声音。
you know, from their voices.
哦 ？
Oh?
县青年说岁月催人老
Young county says same deal
在奥尔尼的分支。
with the branch in olney.
对不起。
Excuse me.
他们有视频吗 ？
Do they have video?
相同的处理。
Same deal all the way around.
没有沃尔玛出售的各类电子装备 ？
Doesn't Walmart sell all sorts of electronic equipment?
我的话。 拿开你的手。
My word. Get your hands off that.
好吧 ， 这些孩子 ， 他们的工作还远没有结束 ， 我就告诉你。
Well, these boys, they aren't done yet, I'll tell you that.
怎么会呢 ？ 嗯 ， 他们很有耐心。
How come? Well, they're patient.
仅仅对抽屉
Just sticking to the drawers,
不 ， 那是银行的钱
not taking the hundreds, that's the bank's money,
我们可追查。
we can trace that.
他们试图提出一个确定的量 ， 这是我的猜测。
They're trying to raise a certain amount, that's my guess.
这需要几个银行。
It's gonna take a few banks to get there.
你知道他们怎么富 ？
Your boys know how rich they're gonna be?
他们不知道事情的全部。
They don't know anything yet.
你带他们去葬礼 ？
You take them to the funeral?
就像我说的 ， 他们根本不知道。
Like I said, they don't know anything.
上次你看见没有 ？
When's the last time you saw them?
当我们都去了斯坦福在竞技结束后马上就出来了。
When we all went to the rodeo in stamford right after you got out.
那是一年前。 我跟他们交谈的电话。
That was a year ago. I talk to them on the phone.
你跟他们打电话吗 ？
You talk to them on the phone?
你需要一些建议吗 ？ 没有。 不 ， 我不要。
You want a little advice? No. No, I don't.
明天去见他们。
Go see them tomorrow.
你知道多少我欠 Debbie 在子女抚养费 ？
You got any idea how much I owe Debbie in child support?
你有在你前面
You've got enough in your front pocket
为解决这个问题。
to fix that problem right now.
我们不能少了它 ， 你知道。
We can't spare it, you know that.
也许我们应该打击另一个分支。
Maybe we should hit another branch.
你知道 ， 你说我们不会逍遥法外。 ”
You know, you talk like we ain't gonna get away with this.
我从没见过任何人带东西的。 你呢 ？
I've never met nobody who got away with anything, ever. You?
那么为什么在地狱你会同意吗 ？
Then why in the hell did you agree to do it?
因为你问我 ， 小哥哥。
Because you asked, little brother.
我就像一只老山羊。
I got to shit like an old goat.
抓检查 ， 见我出来前。
Grab the check, meet me out front.
好吧 ， 如果不是一个暗示 ，
Well, if that isn't a hint,
我不知道是什么。
I don't know what is.
你的牛排要几分熟 ？
You like your steak?
是的 ， 夫人。
Yes, ma'am.
好吧 ， 你还有很长的路要走。
Well, you've got a ways to go yet.
是啊 ， 你等了一整天来完成这个。
Yeah, you'll be waiting around all day for me to finish this.
我在这儿你是否完成。 . 所以..
I'll be here whether you finish it or not. So...
你把你的时间。
You take your time.
它在这里肯定很安静。
It sure is quiet in here.
打开抽屉。 五、 10s 、 20s 。
Open the drawer. Fives, 10s, 20s.
风扇像一副扑克牌。
Fan them out like a deck of cards.
你是做什么的 ？
What do you do?
最后一份工作是对的。..
Last job was for a...
天然气公司。
Natural gas company.
声音高美元。
Sounds high-dollar.
没有 ， 什么都没有 ， 而高美元左右。
No, there ain't nothing high-dollar about drilling.
似乎没有人在钻探天然气现在 ， 不管怎样。
No one seems to be drilling for gas now, anyway.
他们肯定钻探石油。
They sure drilling for oil.
我的意思是 ， 一个钻的吗 ？
I mean, ain't one drill the same as the next?
这是我的看法。
That's my take on it.
我猜 ， 我得让别人相信我。
I guess, I got to get someone else to believe me.
狗娘养的 ！
Son of a bitch!
我们需要个厨师。
We could use a cook.
只是一个想法。
Just a thought.
从而 ， 珍妮安。
Order's up, Jenny Ann.
再见。
Bye.
启动汽车 ！
Start the car!
狗屎。
Shit.
操 ！ 狗屎 ！
Fuck! Shit!
走 ， 走 ， 走 ！
Go, go, go!
我打赌你不欠这孩子太多的支持。
I bet you don't owe this much in child support.
我他妈的想请你帮忙。
I must be out of my goddamn mind to ask you for help.
你想害死我们吗 ？ 嗯 ？
You wanna get us killed? Huh?
这不是英格兰中部地区的分支。
That's not a Midlands branch.
这不是计划的一部分。
That's not part of the plan.
现在 ， 我们开始回到牧场 ， 看看那些汽车。 他妈的 ！
Now, we got to go back to the ranch and bury the car. Fuck!
不 ， 我们不做。 我们走完了一半。
No, we do not. We're over halfway to Oklahoma.
我不开车偷来的汽车逃跑
I'm not driving a stolen getaway car
去他妈的印第安人赌场。
to a fucking Indian casino.
你只是把我们他妈的一天。
You just put us a goddamn day behind.
好吧 ， 我给我们买了第二天早上 ， 我想我们甚至。
Well, I got us a day ahead this morning, so I guess we're even.
欢迎你。 他妈的你。
You're welcome. Fuck you.
你不能回答你的电话吗 ？
Can't you answer your own phone?
我开车。 你只是坐在那里抚弄你的胖手指。
I'm driving. You're just sitting there twiddling your fat fingers.
游侠汉密尔顿的电话。
Ranger Hamilton's phone.
这一点也是这样。 哦。..
It's reckless is what it is. Oh...
它的修改者借机。 我告诉你。
It's tweakers. I'm telling you.
我不认为这些男孩子是鲁莽。
I don't think these boys is reckless.
肯定不是修改者借机。
Damn sure ain't tweakers.
他们知道他们究竟在做什么。
They know exactly what they're doing.
我不知道你怎么生存
I don't know how you're gonna survive
没有其他人。
without somebody to outsmart.
你需要一个爱好 ， 和快速。
You need a hobby, and quick.
怎么样的马 ？
How about a horse?
玛丽贝丝的骑车人。
Mary Beth was the rider.
马只想起她来。
A horse would only remind me of her.
你喜欢鱼。
You like to fish.
不多 ， 要全力反击。
Not enough to do it every goddamn day.
是啊 ， 当我退休时 ，
Yeah, when I retire,
我要把我对艾思梅和加尔维斯敦。
I'm gonna move Esme and me down to galveston.
购买了一艘渔船。
Buy a fishing boat.
要住在那个狗娘养的 ， 右一个 “家” 。
Gonna live on that son of a bitch right at the pier.
哦 ， 谁知道呢 ？
Oh, who knows?
也许这些银行劫匪
Maybe one of these bank robbers
想要一场枪战 ，
is gonna want a gunfight,
我和我的退休可以在一刹那间产生的荣耀。
and I can dodge my retirement in a Blaze of glory.
我见过你射击的。
Well, I've seen you shoot.
将不会有多少荣耀。
There won't be much glory in it.
哦 ， 嗯 ， 我很幸运
Oh, well, I'm lucky
我是个杂种在我身边为我报仇。
I got a half-breed by my side to avenge me.
如果你能保持清醒足够长。
If you can stay sober long enough.
知道你喜欢印第安人的瓶子。
Knowing how you injuns like the bottle.
哇。
Whoa.
嘿。 什么你们都还好吗 ？
Hey. What you all doing?
你要烧吗 ？
You burning this field?
为何会在狗屎 ？
Why in the shit would we do that?
这引发了对公路、
This kicked up on the highway,
我们的追求目标。
been chasing us ever since.
希望我们能为你做点什么。
Wish we could do something for you.
应该让它把我的骨灰
Ought to just let it turn me to ashes
把我干掉了。
and put me out of my misery.
剪篱笆。
Cut that fence.
21 世纪 ，
21st century,
我就在河流的牛群。
I'm racing a fire to the river with a herd of cattle.
我想知道为什么我的孩子不会做这该死的生活。
And I wonder why my kids won't do this shit for a living.
移动它。 来吧。
Move it. Come on.
走 ， 走 ， 走。
Go, go, go.
你想叫它在吗 ？
You wanna call it in?
哦 ， 我要烧了这布拉索斯。
Oh, it's gonna burn out when it hits the brazos.
没有人打电话到这里来。
No one to call around here, anyway.
这些孩子是自己的。
These boys is on their own.
我仍然不明白这个问题 ， 托比。
I still don't see the problem, Toby.
你仍然不。.. 但问题是 ， 谢谢你
You still don't... Well, the problem is, thanks to you
我们明天早上要上另一辆车 ，
we have to spend tomorrow morning getting another car,
所以我们不得不打两个银行。
so we'll have to hit two banks on Wednesday.
今天我们已经做过三次。
We already done three today.
停止忧虑。
Stop worrying.
谁的土地 ？
Whose land is this?
Jeremy 乔克。
Jeremy chalker.
他让我住在这里拍摄的土狼。
He lets me stay here in exchange for shooting coyotes.
冷啤酒在冰箱里。
Cold beer in the fridge.
你偷了我的帽子。
You stole my hat.
我借的.
I borrowed it.
你他妈的做什么呢 ？
What the fuck you do to it?
这是什么 ？ 我的生活。
What's this? My livelihood.
我们不需要这一切。
We don't need all this.
只能在拖车。
Can't keep the guns in the trailer days on end.
这不是与我们的银行。
That's not coming with us in the bank.
刚才谈到了柜员。
Just spoke to the teller.
她有点被吓坏了。
She's a little shook up.
凶手拿走了她的驾照 ，
Perp took her driver's license,
威胁她 ， 如果她跟我们家人。
threatened her family if she talked to us.
介意我问你你叫什么名字 ， 小姐 ？
Mind if I ask you your name, young lady?
娜塔丽 ・ 马丁内兹。
Natalie Martinez.
纳塔丽 ， 我想让你知道
Well, Natalie, i want you to know
我们会有一些军官
we're gonna have some officers
看你的房子 ， 格外小心
watching your house, extra careful,
直到我们抓住这些坏蛋。
till we catch these buggers.
你也得承担责任。
You have my word on that.
不止一个 ？
There's more than one?
只有一个人打劫银行 ？
Only one man robbed the bank?
是啊。 他看起来怎么样 ？
Yeah. What'd he look like?
他打扮得像牛仔除了滑雪面罩。
He was dressed like a cowpoke except for the ski mask.
我想他的汽车跑去
I think he ran to a car
停靠在外面的餐馆。
that was parked out front of the diner.
你看到那辆车了吗 ？
You saw the car?
它是绿色的。
It was green.
多大 ？ 我不知道 ， 先生。
How old? I don't know cars, mister.
嗯 ， 它是一辆漂亮的汽车或汽车的好 ，
Well, was it a nice car or an okay car,
或是一坨大便吗 ？
or a real piece of shit?
它是一个真正的狗屎。
It was a real piece of shit.
好吧。 现在 ， 我们正在取得一些进展。
All right. Now, we're getting somewhere.
哦 ， 看起来好像赎回房子。
Oh, that looks like a man who could foreclose on a house.
对不起 ， 娜塔莉。
Excuse me, Natalie.
对不起 ， 先生。
Excuse me, Mr. banker.
娜塔莉 ， 我要那个警官留下来陪你
Natalie, I'm gonna have the officer stay with you
直到你父亲 ， 没事吧 ？
till your father arrives, all right?
好吧。
Okay.
没了你的监控摄像头
Didn't happen to have your surveillance cameras
在这个早晨 ， 你呢 ？
on this morning, did you?
当然。
Of course.
哦 ， 有了抢劫的录像。
Oh, so you have the robbery on video.
当然我们做。
Of course we do.
什么样的银行将是我们
What kind of bank would we be
如果没有视频监控 ？
if we didn't have video surveillance?
哦 ， 你一定会在德州米德兰银行。
Oh, you'd be a Texas Midlands bank.
好吧 ， 我们有视频。
All right, we've got video.
来的时候看我走到汉堡店吗 ？
Care to give it a watch while I wander over to the burger joint?
我命令你
Would you order me something
你在那儿吗 ？ 我饿死了。
while you're there? I'm starving.
我怀疑他们肉饼。
I doubt they serve pemmican.
你知道我是墨西哥人。
You know I'm part Mexican, too.
好的我去去
Yeah, well, I'm gonna get to that
当我跟印度人的侮辱 ，
when I'm through with the Indian insults,
但这需要一段时间。
but it's gonna be a while.
你是一个奇怪的流浪者。
You rangers are an odd bunch.
不 ， 只是他。 我们先来看看视频。
No, just him. Let's take a look at that video.
就回来这里。
Yeah, it's right back here.
你好。
Howdy.
Ma 'am. 你想知道的一切。
Ma'am. Guess you know about the goings-on at the bank.
我没有注意到它。
I did notice.
任何对外地人过来 ？
Any out-of-towners come through today?
等待在安珍妮夫妇的儿子 ， 对从这里。
Jenny Ann waited on a couple of boys, ain't from here.
哦 ？
Oh?
我去找她。
I'll go get her.
理解。
Appreciate that.
男孩。
Boys.
你们都在这儿吗 ？
Y'all been here for a while?
嗯 ， 观看被抢劫银行
Well, long enough to watch a bank getting robbed
那是我被抢劫了 30 年。
that's been robbing me for 30 years.
哦 ， 你说过吗 ？
Oh, you say you've seen them?
他们应该是坐在
I'm pretty sure they were sitting
就在那儿吃午饭。
right over there having lunch.
其中之一是高大。
One of them was tall.
另一个是短的。
The other one was short.
他们的牛仔都喜欢。
They's both lean like cowboys.
看起来像兄弟会 ， 如果你问我。
Looked like brothers if you ask me.
你这个德州突击队员 ？
You the Texas ranger?
是的 ， 夫人。
Yes, ma'am.
告诉我那些年轻英俊的陌生人 ， 你等着。
Tell me about those handsome young strangers that you waited on.
谁说帅气吗 ？
Who said handsome?
我做到了。
I did.
基于这样的事实 ， 你不满足我在停车场 ，
Based on the fact that you didn't meet me in the parking lot,
关于对两个外地人
hollering about the two out-of-towners
在这里吃饭之前抢劫一家银行。
eating here right before a bank robbery.
嗯 ， 他们没有提到他们正在抢劫银行。
Well, they didn't mention they was robbing the bank.
他们用现金付吗 ？
They pay cash?
， 犯罪了吗 ？
That a crime now?
他们离开 ？
How much did they leave?
多少钱 ？
How much?
200 美元。
$200.
离开之前 ， 他们抢劫了银行。 . 所以..
And they left it before the bank was robbed. So...
呃 ， 之前该银行被抢。
Uh, before this bank was robbed.
我需要见他们。
I'm gonna need to see them bills.
Ma 'am. 嗯嗯。
Ma'am. Mmm-mmm.
做客的时候 ， 都是证据。
Ma'am, them bills is evidence.
嗯嗯。 如果有证据支持他们的银行劫匪。
Mmm-mmm. It's evidence if they're the bank robbers.
至此 ， 这就是我的秘诀。
Till then, it's my tip.
和一半我的抵押贷款。
And half my mortgage.
所以 ， 你和你的手令 ， 并跟在钱
So, you go out there and you get a warrant, and come after the money
我将使用到得了我女儿的头。
that I will be using to keep a roof over my daughter's head.
他打了一个银行 ， 就像她说。
One man hit the bank, just like she said.
是啊。 格子衬衫 ，
Yeah. Checkered button-down shirt,
牛仔裤、戴着面罩。 它是在录像带上。
jeans, ski mask. It's on the videotapes.
格纹衬衫。 那是他。
Checkered shirt. That was him.
他们坐在那边。 她 200 元小费。
They were sitting right over there. Tipped her $200.
走了许久的描述中 ， 从野蛮女友大厨房。
Go wrestle a description from that big sassy girl in the kitchen.
你不自己动手呢 ？
You didn't get it yourself?
哦 ， 别忘了脱下她的尖端。 我们要核对账单。
Oh, and get that tip from her. We're gonna check them bills.
好运。
Good luck.
是啊 ， 但我预计一些阻力。
Yeah, I'd expect some resistance.
噢 ， 艾伯特 ，
Oh, and, Alberto,
在汽车旅馆打电话 ， 287 ， 把我们的房间。
call that motel on 287, get us a room.
我们要留下来过夜吗 ？
We're gonna stay the night?
嗯 ， 这是最热闹的地方去。
Well, this is where the action is.
似乎很愚蠢。
Seems foolish.
那是什么 ？
What's that?
在天的劫银行
The days of robbing banks
并努力地生活 ， 花点钱。
and trying to live, spend the money.
他们早已不复存在。
They've long gone.
早已不复存在。
Long gone for sure.
贾斯汀想去做什么当他长大了吗 ？
What does Justin want to do when he's grown?
现在他的足球梦想 ， 起吊的 A & M 。
Right now he's dreaming of slinging a football for a&m.
他很像你。
He's a lot like you.
我打赌你的皱纹 ， 眼睛红色。
I bet that puckers your red eye.
你所不知道的东西。
More than you know.
39 岁的生命 ，
Thirty-nine years of life,
10 年监禁。 如果他留下 ， 我得进去 ， 他马上就好。
10 in jail. If he turns left where I turned right, he'll be okay.
偏航。
Yaw.
你要什么吗 ？
You want anything?
Dr. Pepper ， 温斯顿。
Dr. pepper, Winston lights.
It 's okay. 来吧。
It's okay. Come on.
什么 ？
What?
什么 ， 贱货 ？
What, bitch?
你找死吗 ， 混蛋 ？
You looking for trouble, motherfucker?
你来对了地方。
You came to the right place.
男孩 ， 你会认为我是 10 号。
Boy, you'd think there were 10 of me.
哦 ， 是吗 ？
Oh, yeah?
他妈的现在没那么强硬 ， 是吗 ， 婊子 ？
Not so fucking tough now, are you, bitch?
嘿 ， 伙计 ， 他罪有应得。
Hey, man, he had it coming.
他已经来了。 他已经来了。
He had it coming. He had it coming.
你有胆量的话。
You got some spunk left in you.
哦 ， 你记住了枪 ！
Oh, you remembered the gun!
你这是旧帽子。
You're getting to be old hat at this.
混蛋差点杀了你。
Asshole could've killed you.
啊 ， 早就不在了 ， 小兄弟。
Ah, not the way it would have gone, little brother.
10 我的 ， 我告诉你。
Ten of me, I told you.
你是想让我疯了吗 ？
Are you trying to make me mad?
我说 ， 胡椒先生 ， 这位是皮伯。
I said Dr. pepper, this is Mr. pibb.
这是他们仅有的。
That's all they had.
只喝了混蛋先生皮伯。
Only assholes drink Mr. pibb.
喝起来。
Drink up.
你好。
Hello.
现在我们讨论。
Now we're talking.
在这个地方。
The women in this place.
你说什么鬼话 ？
What the hell you talking about?
我们要再拍 ， 他们就会很快。
We should get another shot, they'll be pretty soon enough.
酒保威士忌如果你请。
Bartender, whiskeys if you please.
上来。
Coming up.
对你的男孩。
To your boys.
让我们去改变。
Let's go change that money.
对不起。 我只是卖。 这就是我的家伙。
Sorry. I just sold my car. This is how the fella paid me.
我们也该你拿, 先生.
We take it any way you bring it, mister.
一些想玩扑克吗 ？
Wanna play some poker?
我不赌博。
I don't gamble.
你在扑克中 ， 甚至你。
You can't lose at poker, not even you.
我会看着老师和喝啤酒比赛。
I'm gonna watch the aggie game and have a beer.
随你便。
Suit yourself.
来吧。
Come on now.
吮吸 D 。
Suck a d.
不要失去它。
Don't lose it all.
我吃的。
Eat my a.
他妈的混蛋。
Fucking asshole.
那是 ， 呃 ， 一个堆栈。
That's, uh, quite a stack.
检查吗 ？
Check?
别追我 ， 头儿。
Don't chase me, chief.
科曼奇你吗 ？
You comanche?
大陆的平原。
Lords of the plains.
没有现在的领主。
Lords of nothing now.
我呼叫。
I call.
摊牌 ， 先生们。
Show your cards, gentlemen.
你知道这是什么直升机 ？
Do you know what comanche means?
这意味着永远的敌人。
It means enemies forever.
敌人是谁 ？
Enemies with who?
每个人。
Everyone.
你知道什么让我 ？
You know what that makes me?
一个敌人。
An enemy.
没有。
No.
它让我有一个科曼奇。
It makes me a comanche.
他看起来像你吗 ？
Does he look like you?
我看到他妈妈在他 ，
I see his mom in him,
别人看见我。
everybody else sees me.
我不知道。
I don't know.
你住在酒店里吗 ？
You staying in the hotel?
是啊。
Yeah.
我去你的房间。
Take me to your room.
谢谢你。 只是 ， 嗯..
Thank you. Just, uh...
你知道 ， 没有什么羞愧的地方需要一个女人的触摸。
You know, there's no shame in needing the touch of a woman.
你需要它。
You need it.
我知道你做。
I know you do.
让我触摸你。
Just let me touch you.
你想我的小弟弟吗 ？
Are you trying to work my little brother?
不 ， 我没事情做 ， 但我是。.. Tanner ， 她没有做什么。
No, I wasn't doing anything, but I'm... Tanner, she didn't do nothin'.
她没做什么。 但是 ， 但是 ， 但是 ， 但是 … …..
She didn't do nothin'. But, but, but, but, but...
你看到有一只的筹码堆中。
You saw there was a stack of chips, here.
易受骗的人吗 ？ 不要。
Easy mark? Don't.
嗯.. 没有。
Uh... no.
你要做什么 ？ 他把他的房间
What were you gonna do? Bring him up to his room,
叫你的皮条客 ，
call your pimp,
他卷了 ， 什么 ？ 没有。 我的..
roll him, drug him, what? No. I...
你要做什么 ？ 唐纳 ， 不要。
What were you gonna do? Tanner, don't.
我的货物样品 ？ 真正的..
Mind if I sample the goods? Real...
她的手。 停止它。 停止它。
Hands off her. Stop it. Stop it.
你真是疯了
You're fucking crazy.
打电话给我。
Call me.
有什么问题吗 ？
We got a problem here?
一切都很好。 一切都很好。 一切都很好。
It's all good. It's all good. It's all good.
一切都很好。 我有点醉了
It's all good. Just got a little drunk
在酒吧 ， 抱歉。
at the bar, sorry about that.
如何他妈的你已经
How the fuck have you managed
要坐牢一年 ？
to stay out of prison for a year?
它是困难的。
It's been difficult.
为了该现金还是支票 ？
Like to pay this out in cash or check?
黛比得到一些钱。
Get some Debbie money.
四、休息。
Four in cash, rest in check.
您的支票 ？
Who would you like the check made out to?
德州米德兰银行。
Texas Midlands bank.
谢谢你.
Thank you much.
我们的房间。
Let's go get a room.
欢迎来到 66 “科曼奇” 。 你有预订吗 ？
Welcome to the comanche 66. Do you have a reservation?
我们不做。
We do not.
天哪 ， 看看你。
Good lord, look at you.
我们希望你能提供住宿、
We would be obliged if you would provide accommodations,
虽然未能提前打电话。
though we failed to call ahead.
男孩 ， 你的麻烦。
Boy, you are trouble.
哦 ， 不过了 ， 亲爱的。
Oh, the worst kind, darling.
在最后的时光在家庭护理中 ，
In your last days in the nursing home,
你会想我傻笑。
you'll think of me and giggle.
上帝啊 ， 为什么
Why, god,
你为什么不回答我的祷告 ？
why won't you answer my prayers?
你乞求他的帮助 ，
You begged him for help,
然而你看看你的生活
and yet you look around at your life
并没有什么不同。
and nothing is different.
所以 ， 你认为上帝告诉你没有。
And so you assume that god has told you no.
上帝没有说不。
God doesn't say no.
我们为什么不能回到教练吗 ？
Why couldn't we drive back to lubbock?
他们抢劫银行的时候。
They ain't robbing banks in lubbock.
我们不是要看这个 ， 是吗 ？
We're not gonna watch this, are we?
你不是基督徒吗 ？
Ain't you Christian?
是啊。 但我不是傻瓜。
Yeah. But I ain't stupid.
神没说这人
God doesn't talk through this man
就像我的狗说话。
any more than he talks through my dog.
好吧 ， 那么也许你应该给你的狗听。
Well, then maybe you should give your dog a listen.
那你是印度人吗 ？
Ain't you Indian?
你本来应该点燃鼠尾草香
You're supposed to be burning Sage
和围着床在跳舞欢呼 ， 像蜜蜂蛰你。
and dancing around the bed whooping like a bee stung you.
我是天主教徒。
I'm catholic.
来吧。
Come on.
来吧 ！ 我宁愿跳舞的消防枪。
Come on! I'd rather dance around a fire with a spear.
我宁可让你用长矛刺死我也不看这部。
I'd rather have you stab me with a spear than watch this.
这个狗娘养的 ， 他不会知道上帝
This son of a bitch, he wouldn't know god
如果他就爬上了他的裤腿 ， 并咬了他的小弟弟。
if he crawled up his pant leg and bit him on the pecker.
该死的信道变化。
Change the damn channel.
现在 ， 这 ， 这就是使命。
Now, this, this is what god watches right here.
别担心 ， 他们会有精彩的足球。
Don't worry, they're gonna have soccer highlights on soon enough.
这是墨西哥的一半。
That's for your Mexican half.
哦 ！
Ooh!
哇 ， 看看这小子跑。
Wow, look at this boy run.
长角队要有好的团队。
Longhorns are gonna have a good team this year.
足球 ， 从来不知道。
That soccer, never could understand that.
任何一个 5 岁的不可以做的运动。
Anything a five-year-old can do ain't a sport.
是谁发明的 ？ 阿兹特克人吗 ？
Who invented it? Aztecs?
“头骨周围惹火了他 ， 对吧 ？
Kickin' around skulls or something, right?
听起来像一个科曼奇运动。
Sounds like a comanche sport.
你知道 ， 再过三个星期 ，
You know, in three weeks,
你可以看任何你想上电视。
you can watch whatever you want on TV all day.
该死 ， 你可以现在就做吧。
Hell, you can do it right now in your own room.
哦 ， 那有啥乐趣 ？
Oh, where's the fun in that?
你知道什么 ， 艾伯特 ？
You know what, Alberto?
什么 ？
What?
在一年时间内 ，
In a year's time,
我逗你 ， 小姐。
it's my teasing that you're gonna miss.
你就会放声大笑
It's what you'll laugh about
当你站在我坟和良好的祝愿。
when you stand over my grave and wish me well.
上帝 ， 我希望是明天。
God, I hope that's tomorrow.
哦 ， 这个很好。
Oh, that was a good one.
你会熟悉的。
You'll get the hang of this yet.
这不是太晚了吗 ？
Isn't it getting late for you?
是啊。
Yeah.
嗯 ， 是的。
Yeah, it is.
哦 ， 天哪。 天空。
Oh, heavens above. Heavens above.
看看这些奶子。 你他妈的在开玩笑吗 ？
Look at those titties. Are you fucking kidding me?
你在干什么 ？
What are you doing?
睡在门廊 ， 我的未来。
Sleeping on the porch, practicing my future.
这是很危险的一件事我们的生活。
It's a dangerous thing we do for a living.
你很幸运 ，
You're lucky,
看到完成它。
having seen it through to the end.
我希望我是幸运的。
I hope I'm that lucky.
哦 ， 好吧。
Oh, well.
如果没有我在你身边 ，
Without me by your side,
我怀疑你足够近的地方
I doubt you'd get close enough
对于曾经将再次面临危险。
to a criminal to ever be in danger again.
正当我开始觉得对不起他们。
Just when I was starting to feel sorry for you.
印度人不应该为自己感到难过。
Indians ain't supposed to feel sorry for cowboys.
。
It's the other way around.
这让你的遗嘱执行者 ？
And this makes you the executor?
Mmm - hmm.
Mmm-hmm.
不管他们责备我们 ，
No matter what they charge us with,
他们可以带走。
they can't take it away.
没有办法追踪资金的赌场。
There's no way to trace funds from a casino.
好吗 ？ 一旦获得所述支票给银行 ，
All right? Once you get the checks to the bank,
信任是无可比拟的。
trust is untouchable.
你不能告诉任何人任何事 ， 对吗 ？
You can't tell nobody nothing, right?
嗯 ， 怎么说呢 ？
Well, what is there to tell?
我的意思是 ， 你们赢了钱 ， 赌博 ， 不是吗 ？
I mean, you boys won that money gambling, didn't you?
3.2 万美元还清抵押贷款。
$32,000 pays off the reverse mortgage.
和那些杂种把物业税从 2012 年到现在 ，
And those bastards paid the property tax from 2012 to now,
这是另一个 11000 美元。
that's another $11,000.
所以 ， 43, 000 美元 ， 你可以自由和清晰。
So, $43,000 and you are free and clear.
只要传真给我的贷款人员释放留置权
Just have the loan officer fax me a release of lien,
我和我的租赁经理。
and I'll get that over to the lease manager at chevron.
在该传真卡。
The fax number is on the card.
好吧。
Okay.
你做这笔交易吗 ？
How much you making on this deal?
远不是我。
Not near as much as I'm risking.
你为什么那么做 ？
Why you doin' it then?
你知道 ， 他们也只能借给他们。
You know, they loaned the least they could.
我的工作只是让你可怜的妈妈的保证收益。
Just enough to keep your mama poor on a guaranteed return.
她以为他们可以刷卡土地售价 25000 美元。
Thought they could swipe her land for $25,000.
就这样嚣张 ， 它让我的牙齿受到伤害。
That's just so arrogant, it makes my teeth hurt.
你看到男孩
To see you boys
支付这些杂种回自己的钱吗 ？
pay those bastards back with their own money?
好吧 ， 如果你不给 ， 我不知道是什么。
Well, if that ain't texan, i don't know what is.
谢谢你。
Thank you.
现在 ， 他们可以排除。
Now, they can foreclose on Friday.
无论碰到什么困难 ，
Come hell or high water,
在银行查尔德里斯。
be at the bank in childress on Thursday.
白痴 ， 他们知道 ， 他们会提前关闭。
Knowing them fuckers, they will close early.
我们就在这里。 噢 ， 托比 ，
We'll be there. Oh, and, Toby,
所述信任需要由银行托管。
the trust needs to be managed by a bank.
真的很想你无迹可循?
You really wanna cover your tracks?
德州米德兰处理你得到这种信任。
You get Texas midland to handle this trust.
所以 ，
So,
有什么计划吗 ？
what's the plan?
我们要再看银行像鹿。
We're gonna watch that bank like a deer feeder.
随着时间的推移 ， 我们会正确。
In time, we'll be right.
现在 ， 让我们看到什么他们到这里吃。
Now, let's see what they got to eat here.
你好 ， 女士。 你今天怎么样 ？
Howdy, ma'am. How are you doing today?
热。 我并不是很好。
Hot. And I don't mean the good kind.
所以 ， 你想要什么 ？
So, what don't you want?
再说一遍 ， 好吗 ？
Pardon?
你想要什么 ？
What don't you want?
哦 ， 嗯 ， 嗯 ， 我想我只是 ， 嗯..
Oh, well, uh, i think I'll just, uh...
你知道 ， 我在这里工作了 44 年。
You know, I've been working here for 44 years.
你曾吩咐过 ，
Ain't nobody ever ordered nothing
但 T - 骨牛排和烤土豆。
but t-bone steak and a baked potato.
除了这个从纽约一个混蛋
Except this one asshole from New York
想要订购鳟鱼早在 1987 年。
tried to order trout back in 1987.
我们不出售任何他妈的鳟鱼。
We don't sell no goddamned trout.
T 骨牛排。
T-bone steaks.
所以 ， 你不想煮玉米 ，
So, either you don't want the corn on the cob,
还是不要绿豆。
or you don't want the green beans.
所以 ， 你想要什么 ？
So, what don't you want?
我不想要青豆。
I don't want green beans.
I don't want green beans either.
半生熟牛排。
Steaks cooked medium rare.
我要的牛排。.. 不 ， 没有问题。
Can I get my steak cooked... That weren't no question.
好吧。
All right.
男孩你的冰茶。
Iced tea for you boys.
冰茶就好了。
Iced tea would be great.
冰茶。 谢谢你 ， 夫人。
Iced tea, yep. Thank you, ma'am.
嗯嗯。
Uh-huh.
哦 ， 我告诉你一件事。
Well, I'll tell you one thing.
没有人会夺走了这个狗娘养的。
Nobody's gonna rob this son of a bitch.
我的话。
My word.
她感觉怎样 ？
How's she feel?
她很好。
She runs good.
不会赢得任何比赛。
Ain't gonna win any races.
还有新墨西哥州。
Got new Mexico plates.
她有顶吗 ？
She got a top?
这就是她。
That's how she came.
我们要用她。
We'll take her.
它不报导直到星期五被盗。
Don't report it stolen until Friday.
这家伙从雪佛龙被脱落的租赁协议。
The guy from chevron is dropping off the lease agreement.
是的 ， 你还好吗 ？
Are you okay dealing with that by yourself?
黛比 ， 你还好吗 ？
You okay being with Debbie by yourself?
记住 ， 他不是敌人。
Remember, he ain't the enemy.
就拿报纸 ， 说谢谢你。
Just take the papers, and say thank you.
敌人是男人的油 ，
The oil man is the enemy,
不犯错误。 他根本不是我们的。
make no mistake. He just ain't ours.
我将回到黑暗的牧场。
I'll be back to the ranch by dark.
我还会来的。
I will be waiting.
开车像一个老师 ， 都在后面。
Drive like a schoolteacher with all this shit in the back.
肯定感觉象啤酒。
Sure feels like beer o'clock.
问你应接受。
Ask and you shall receive.
进来。
Come in.
妈妈死了。
Mama died.
当吗 ？
When?
几个星期前。
A few weeks ago.
嗯 ， 太好了。
Well, good riddance.
没有冒犯的意思。
No offense.
你还好吗 ？
You okay?
你呢 ？
You?
这是我欠你的钱。
Here's the money i owe you.
我猜你会卖掉这个牧场。
I guess you'll be selling the ranch.
那男孩。
It goes to the boys.
真的吗 ？ MMM 。
Really? Mmm.
它的信任。
It's been put in a trust.
那是什么意思 ？
What's that mean?
这意味着任何人都可以把它卖了。
It means no one can sell it.
伟大。 另外我还得照顾。
Great. Something else i got to take care of.
Hi 。
Hi.
你弟弟呢 ？
Where's your brother?
我不知道。
I don't know.
朋友的房子 ， 我猜。
Friend's house, i guess.
为什么你不在学校吗 ？
How come you ain't in school?
学校还没有开始。
School don't start yet.
只有 2 天的足球现在。
Just two-a-days for football right now.
你外婆去世。
Your grandmother died.
我就把这个送给你和你的兄弟。
I'm giving the ranch to you and your brother.
记得去那儿了吗 ？
Remember going out there when you was little?
给我干嘛农场 ？
What am I supposed to do with a ranch?
但它卖什么。
Anything but sell it.
我们发现石油。
We found oil on it.
你和你弟弟不会再无须为钱担心了。
You and your brother ain't gonna have to worry about money no more.
现在 ，
Now,
你可以听到很多关于我的事
you may be hearing a lot of things about me
你的叔叔。
and your uncle.
不喜欢我们。
Don't be like us.
你听到我说话吗 ？
You hear me?
我听到了 ， 我不会相信。
Whatever I hear, i won't believe.
不 ， 你相信它。
No, you believe it.
我做的这一切。
I did all of it.
现在 ， 你 ， 你不这么干。
Now, you, you do it different.
不喝吗 ？
Ain't gonna drink it?
告诉我你不喜欢你 ，
You tell me not to be like you,
然后你给我一杯啤酒。
and then you offer me a beer.
这是它吗 ？
Which is it?
好男孩。
Good boy.
孩子们怎么样? 你干什么 ？
How are the boys? What are you doin'?
保险。
Insurance.
我不想要那该死的车。
I don't want that shit in the car.
我们将接着运行两个车 ， 兄弟。
We'll be running two cars next time, brother.
他们与我同行。
They'll ride with me.
所以 ， 这就是你的计划 ？
So, this is your plan?
我们只是坐在这里
We're just gonna sit here
看看这个被他们抢劫的分支。
and see if this is the branch they rob next.
你要干什么 ？
What would you rather do?
你要开车 80 英里回奥尔尼
You wanna drive 80 miles back to olney
寻找更多的指纹 ， 我们不会发现 ？
and look for more fingerprints that we ain't gonna find?
或者你想开车 200 英里回到 Lubbock
Or you wanna drive 200 miles back to lubbock
看照片并不重要
and look at mug shots that don't matter
因为没有人知道这些狗娘养的样子。
because nobody knows what these sons of bitches look like.
或者我们可以在这儿等他们抢劫这家银行 ，
Or we can just wait here for them to rob this bank,
这是我很该死肯定要做的。
which is the one thing I'm pretty damn sure they are going to do.
我知道你在做什么。
I know what you're doing.
你想让这个过去吧 ， 因为这种情况持续时间越长 ，
You're trying to make this last as long as you can because the longer it lasts,
越远 ， 从门廊前。
the farther you are from that front porch.
没有 ， 我在等这些孩子犯了错误。
No, I'm waitin' for these boys to make a mistake.
到目前为止他们 ， 但他们会。
So far they ain't, but they will.
他们想在这里。
And they're gonna make it here.
所以 ， 稍稍地放松心情。
So, just relax.
享受幸福。
Enjoy this little town.
你想住在这里吗 ？
Do you wanna live here?
倒是有 ， 费用双倍五金商店 (Home Depot) ，
Got an old hardware store that charges twice what home depot does,
有一个餐厅服务生的响尾蛇。
one restaurant with a rattlesnake for a waitress.
我是说 ， 谁让这里的生活吗 ？
I mean, how is anybody supposed to make a living here?
一个人在这儿生活了 150 年。
People have made a living here for 150 years.
人们住在山洞里的 15 万。
Well, people lived in caves for 150,000 years.
但他们没有做它。
But they don't do it no more.
好吧 ， 也许你的人。
Well, maybe your people did.
你的人也是。
Your people did, too.
很久以前 ， 印第安人是你祖宗 ，
A long time ago, your ancestors was the Indians,
直到有人出现并杀了他们
till someone came along and killed them,
把他们放下 ， 把你变成他们中的一员。
broke 'em down, made you into one of them.
150 年前 ， 所有的这是我祖先的土地。
150 years ago, all of this was my ancestors' land.
你能看到一切。
Everything you could see.
你昨天看到的一切。
Everything you saw yesterday.
直到爷爷奶奶的人了。
Till the grandparents of these folks took it.
而现在 ， 它是原有的。
And now, it's been taken from them.
但它不是军队。
Except it ain't no army doing it.
这个狗娘养的 ！
It's those sons of bitches right there.
你想明天 ？
You thinking about tomorrow?
不是吗 ？
Ain't you?
那个小旅馆职员。
That little hotel clerk.
为什么总是那么的甜粽
Why is it always the sweet ones
这样 ， 当你是魔鬼让他们兴奋起来了呢 ？
that are such devils when you get them revved up?
不知道 ， 从来没有一个甜一个。
Wouldn't know, never had a sweet one.
是啊 ， 你觉得很生气。
Yeah, you like them pissed off,
找替罪羊。
lookin' for someone to blame.
肯定是这样。
Sure seems that way.
幸好你在干什么。
It's a good thing you're doing.
我们正在做它。
We're doing it.
银行柜员的明天。
Go easy on the bank teller tomorrow.
我会老实的年轻护士。
I'll be as gentle as a young nurse.
你来吗 ？
You coming?
在路上了。
On my way.
嘿。
Hey.
狗屎。
Shit.
早晨好。
Good morning.
你想一些早餐吗 ？
You want some breakfast?
是的 ， 早餐不错。
Yeah, breakfast sounds good.
所以我们击中了杰顿第一分支 ， 然后 ， 对吗 ？
So we hit the jayton branch first, then Coleman, right?
对 ， 这让我们所需要的。
Yeah, that should get us what we need.
让我们这样做的。
Let's do this.
啊该死.. 。
Ugh... shit.
这他妈的不是计划的一部分。
That's not part of the fucking plan.
混蛋关闭分支。
Bastards closed down the branch.
什么现在吗 ， 小弟 ？
What now, little brother?
科尔曼。
Coleman.
什么是地狱你在干什么 ？
What the hell you doing?
我们得为后。
We gotta head to post.
什么是地狱你在干什么 ？ 让。..
What the hell you doing? Get...
我们要去头。 你说什么呢 ？
We got to head to post. What are you talking about?
我们要去头。
We got to head to post.
我们将科尔曼。
We're going to Coleman.
只有一个人科尔曼。
There's only one teller in Coleman.
无论我们是不够的。
Whatever we get won't be enough.
现在我们转到科尔曼。
We go to Coleman right now.
如果这不是足够 ， 头部向后。
If that ain't enough, we head to post.
如果我们不能离开现在的岗位 ，
If we don't leave now for post,
我们不会到中午。
we won't get there till noon.
你不想在午餐时间去抢银行 ， 是吗 ？
You don't wanna rob a bank at lunchtime, do you?
是啊 ， 我们不知道的人。
Yeah, we don't know the patterns of folks out there.
这些图案都是一样的。
The patterns are the same everywhere.
这些城都是死。 后没有不同。
All these towns are dead. Post ain't no different.
它的大银行。
It's a bigger bank.
看看你的汽车就出门了。
We'll leave your car just out of town.
来吧。
Come on now.
狗屎。
Shit.
我觉得我有这种情况。
I think I got this figured.
两个第一银行 ， 他们分别是得克萨斯州米德兰银行。
First two banks, they were Texas midland banks.
好吧 ， 有七家分公司。
All right, there are seven branches altogether.
主要分支是在沃思堡。
The main branch is in fort worth.
他们不会扰乱。
They're not gonna mess with that.
好吗 ？ 他们在奥尔良分支。
All right? They hit the branch in olney.
他们在一个城市中。
They hit the one in Archer city.
然后还有一个在这里。
Then there's the one here.
他们没有击中。
Which they did not hit.
艾伯特 ， 你会请吗 ？ ”
Alberto, will you please follow me?
只是闭上你的嘴
Just keep your mouth shut
且先听我说。
and just listen to what I'm gonna say.
这里有一个 ，
There's the one here,
还有一个在切。
then there's the one in childress.
这是一个在杰顿。
There's the one in jayton.
一个封闭的。
That one's closed.
我知道一个人的 ！
I know that one's closed!
我知道 ， 一个已经关门 ， 阿尔贝托。
I know that one's closed, Alberto.
我就是这么想的。 杰顿。
That's my point. Jayton is closed.
刚刚离开岗位。
That just leaves post.
他们不会在餐厅与银行 Childress,
They're not gonna mess with the bank in childress,
那是一个相当不错的。
that's a fairly decent-sized town.
在分支的中部哈 ， 两人一见钟情。
The branch in Vernon wasn't Midlands and they hit that.
是啊 ， 一个不戴。 孤单。
Yeah, one of them did. Alone.
然后他一路跑到马路对面去了。
Then he ran all the way across the road to get to the car.
我认为他的搭档都不知道会发生这种事。
I think his partner had no idea that was gonna happen.
这意味着什么呢 ？
And what does that mean to us?
它只意味着分支 ， 是在后的为准。
It means that the only branch that fits the bill is in post.
好吧 ， 那我们走吧。
Well, then let's go.
这个镇看上去很忙碌。
The town looks busy.
接受我们的采访。
Little bit.
我的话。
My word.
世界太大。
It's too big.
这就是她说。
That's what she said.
挺好的。
It's no good.
哦 ， 这不是第一次拍戏。
Aw, this ain't your first rodeo.
大银行的方案。
Bigger bank.
更多的钱。
More money.
每个人 ， 该死的 ！
Everybody, get on the fucking ground!
给我上 ！
Get on the fucking ground!
小姐们 ， 去他妈的 ！ 现在 ！
Young ladies, get on the fucking ground! Now!
先生 ， 放下 ！ 在地面上 ！ 现在 ！
Sir, down! On the ground! Now!
非常谢谢你。
Thank you very much.
出纳员站起来 ！
Tellers stand up!
打开柜子 ！
Open the drawers!
趴下 ！
Get down!
退后 ！
Take three steps back!
打开该死的抽屉 ， 小姐 ！
Open the fucking drawer, young lady!
你是聋了还是傻了 ？
Are you deaf and dumb?
我说他妈的抽屉打开 ！
I said open the motherfucking drawer!
你 ， 趴下 ！
You, down!
现在, 后退一步 ！
Now, step back!
非常好。 有人关注。
Very good. Someone's paying attention.
现在 ， 你他妈的膝盖!
Now, get on your motherfucking knees!
嘿 ！
Hey!
趴下 ！ 趴下 ！
Stay down!
好的。
All right.
嘿 ， 嘿 ， 我们走吧 ！
Hey, hey, let's go!
呼叫 911 。
Call 911.
耶稣他妈的基督。
Jesus fucking Christ.
整个该死的小镇射击。
The whole goddamn town is shooting at us.
坐后排。 获得他妈的回来了。
Get in the back. Get in the fucking back.
快点 ， 我们走 ， 上车 ！
Come on, let's go, get in the car!
别让他们跑掉 ！
Don't let them get away!
你在那儿干吗呢 ， 小兄弟 ？
How you doing back there, little brother?
你他妈的杀了他们。
You fucking killed them.
那些隐藏携带许可确定复杂的银行抢案 ， 不是吗 ？
Those concealed carry permits sure complicate a bank robbery, don't they?
这不是我的错发工资了。
It's not my fault it was payday.
这已经走得太远了。
This has gone too far, tan.
没有人是他妈的死。
No one was supposed to fucking die.
这是我们或者他们 ， 你挑吧。
It was them or us, take your pick.
是啊 ， 走 ， 玛格丽特。
Yeah, go, Margaret.
米德兰在德克萨斯州后被击中。
Texas Midlands in post has just been hit.
啊 ！ 我告诉过你吗 ？
Ah! What did I tell you?
是啊。
Yeah.
是啊。 当地人都在追逐。
Yeah. Locals are in chase.
嫌疑人在逃逸的老西部野马。
Suspects escaping west in an old bronco.
好吧 ， 玛格丽特 ， 告诉我们。
All right, Margaret, keep us posted.
我们在路上。
We're on our way there.
给我印度的呐喊声。 来吧。
Give me an Indian whoop. Come on.
这些男孩们会惩罚他们。
These boys gonna go down.
我们跟上音乐。
Let's get some giddy-up music going on there.
哦 ， 请 ， 没有。
Oh, please, not that.
是啊。
Yeah.
嘿 ， 嘿。 来吧。 打起精神来。
Hey, hey. Come on. Snap out of it.
卡扣吧。
Snap the fuck out of it.
妈 ， 让我看看。 你中弹了吗 ？
Shit, let me see that. You're hit.
男孩 ， 你中弹了吗 ？ 拿了回来。
Boy, you're hit. Get the back.
嗯 ， 你不会死的。 它的通过和通过。
Well, you'll live. It's a through and through.
压缩它。 总结了。
Compress it. Wrap it up.
你要适时地总结。
You got to wrap it up tight.
正面和背面 ， 正面和背面。
Front and back, front and back.
它紧密包裹。
Wrap it tight.
哦 ， 兄弟 ， 现在要听从我 ， 我清楚的听到。
Oh, brother, hear me now, hear me clear.
除非你想被一个黑色的痕迹 ， 你的儿子一天天长大 ，
Unless you wanna be a black mark on your sons' lives,
我需要你美洲狮的意思。
I need you mountain lion mean.
你听到我说话吗 ？
You hear me?
我听到你。
I hear you.
美洲狮的意思。 是啊。
Mountain lion mean. Yeah.
是啊。 没事的 ， 没事的。
Yeah. It's gonna be okay, it's gonna be okay.
坚持住。 是啊。
Hold on. Yeah.
去。
Go.
这里 ， 拿了钱。
Here, take the money.
让我们去。 进入赌场 ，
Let's go. Get to the casino,
和我们改变了计划。
change the money like we planned.
这是你的计划。 和它的工作。
This was your plan. And it worked.
每一步的方式。
Every step of the way.
信任它。
Trust it.
你去哪里?
Where are you headed?
不要做傻事。
Don't be stupid.
我喜欢你 ， 托比。
I love you, Toby.
我是认真的。
I mean it.
我也爱你。
I love you, too.
嘿 ， 去你妈的。
Hey, tobe, go fuck yourself.
去你妈的。
Go fuck yourself.
YIPPEE hiyiyo 。 你的小狗。
Yippee hiyiyo. You little doggies.
这就是人们常说的直觉。
This is what they call white man's intuition.
盲人有时猪找到松露。
Sometimes a blind pig finds a truffle.
后退! 噢 ， 该死 ！
Back up! Oh, shit!
去 ！ 移动 ！
Go! Move!
我的话。
My word.
好吧。 我们需要在这里特警组
All right. We're gonna need a SWAT unit up here
这些引脚和 HELO 到男孩。
and a helo to pin these boys down.
I 'm on it.
I'm on it.
嫌疑人是一名男性白人。
Suspect is a white male.
他有枪。 趴下。
He's got a rifle. Get down.
他在山脊上 ！ 他在山脊上 ！
He's on the Ridge! He's on the Ridge!
来吧 ！ 我看见他啦 ！
Come on! I see him!
只有一个吗 ？
There's just one?
对 ， 只是一个。
Yep, just one.
这里本来应该是两个人。
There's supposed to be two of them.
也许有一个镇的人。
Maybe the town folks got one.
好吧 ， 如果他们没有 ， 他们的精明人。
Well, if they did, they got the smart one.
这个男孩 ， 他疯了。
This old boy is out of his mind.
为什么不你这个峡谷和战斧
Why don't you slip up this canyon and tomahawk
那个狗娘养的吗 ？
that son of a bitch?
游侠。 调用该函数。
Ranger down. Call it in.
回来。 背。 那些卡车后面。
Get back. Back. Back those trucks up.
回来。
Get back.
这些卡车。
Get these trucks back.
备份。
Back up.
他们的后台。
Back them up.
你认识这儿周围的土地 ？
How well you know the land around here?
了如指掌。
Like the back of my hand.
好吧。 他藏在山上 ， 刷。
All right. He's hid up in that brush on that hill.
你能给我支持他呢 ？
Can you get me up there behind him?
给我半个小时 ， 我让那个混蛋
Give me a half hour, I'll have that bastard
现场穿上我的卡车。
field dressed on the hood of my truck.
我不能让你那么做。 你刚把我带到那里。
I can't let you do that. You just get me there.
这个可能是一个 500 码的地方 ， 如果他说你。
That's gonna be a 500-yard shot if he's where you said.
只要我有 ！
Just get me there!
狗屎。
Shit.
你还好吗 ？
How are you doing?
好的。 你呢 ？
Good. You?
你去哪里?
Where are you headed?
鲁伊多索。
Ruidoso.
你从哪里来 ？
Where you from?
哈姆林。
Hamlin.
风景美不胜收的路线呢 ？
Taking the scenic route?
只有这样我才能服用。
Taking the only way I can.
他们在公路封闭。
They got the road closed at post.
你所到之处他们封闭了道路。
Everywhere you turn they got the road closed.
你有驾照吗 ？ 是的 ， 我做。
You got your license on you? Yes, I do.
就在那儿等待。
Wait right there.
是的 ， 先生。
Yes, sir.
爵士。 是啊。
Sir. Yeah.
你有个美好的一天。
Have a good day.
谢谢。
Thanks much.
你很臭。
You're pretty winded.
你们应该让我拍了。 该死 ， 这是我的枪。
Y'oughta let me take the shot. Hell, it's my gun.
一点也没有。 他是我的。
Not on your life. He's mine.
左侧的树。
Just left of the tree.
我抓住他了。
I got him.
我抓住你了
I got you.
《平原。
Lord of the plains.
这就是我。
That's me.
..then 。就像公共汽车 ，
...then like something out of a dime-store novel,
德州公路巡警和当地人
Texas highway patrol and the locals
把劫匪我身后的这个山坡 ，
chased the robbers to this hillside behind me,
20 公里外的镇上 ，
20 miles west of town,
在继续枪战。 而现在我们知道
where the gunfight continued. And right now we do know
游侠杀了马库斯汉密尔顿枪手
ranger Marcus Hamilton killed one of the gunmen
他使用一支步枪实际上是从本地居民。
using a rifle he actually borrowed from a resident here.
我们不知道那嫌疑人。..
We don't know the name of that suspect yet...
幸运的家伙。
Lucky guy.
就是在这个时候 ， 太。
Just in the Nick of time, too.
你还好吗 ？
What are the odds?
现在 ， 这个 ， 呃 ， 满足
Now, this, uh, satisfies
反向抵押贷款的 ， 嗯..
both the reverse mortgage loan and the, uh...
税收和我们的母亲。
And the back taxes that we've paid on your mother's behalf.
我们所做的 ， 当然。
We do that as courtesy, of course.
您可以传真留置权释放的数量。
You can fax the release of lien to that number.
律师了吗 ？
An attorney?
好吧。 嗯 ， 我。..
All right. Well, I'll...
我传真到你的律师去了。
I'll get that faxed over to your attorney by the end of the week.
它是在周末。 我想看你做它。
It is the end of the week. I wanna watch you do it.
那是需要一些时间准备。
Well, it takes a little time to prepare.
我整天都有。
I got all day.
好吧。 这就是它。
Okay. That's it.
和真高兴和你做生意。
And it's been a pleasure doing business with you.
让我问你一个问题。
Let me ask you a question.
你们做信托管理 ？
Do y'all manage trusts?
嘿 ， 马库斯 ， 你不是退休了吗 ？
Hey, Marcus, ain't you supposed to be retired?
你好。
Howdy.
很高兴见到你。
Nice to see you.
嗯 ， 嘿 ， 马库斯。
Well, hey, Marcus.
嗨 ， 玛格丽特。
Hey, Margaret.
已一段时间。 生活如平民 ？
Been awhile. How's life as a civilian?
哦 ， 只是 ， 你知道的..
Oh, just, you know...
我可以看看他的档案给我吗 ？
Think I can take a peek at Mr. Howard's file?
Tanner Howard 。
Tanner Howard.
哦 ， 来吧。 我没有别的事做。
Oh, come on. I ain't got nothing better to do.
它在我的书桌。
It's at my desk.
. 呃..
Uh...
哦。
Oh.
杀了他父亲在一次打猎事故 ？
He killed this father in a hunting accident, huh?
我也很想知道他在谷仓的狩猎在 4 月。
I'd love to know what he was hunting in the barn in April.
10 年因故意伤害罪在亨茨维尔。
Ten years in huntsville for aggravated assault.
在 2012 年释放的狱友。
Cellmate was released in 2012.
在此之前 ， 他七年 ；
Before that, he served seven years
在银行抢劫指控的弹簧。
on bank robbery charges up in big spring.
一直在跟踪他 ， 目前为止还是没消息。
Been trying to track him down, but no luck so far.
你所有的兄弟吗 ？
You all are off the brother?
没有什么能联系到他的抢劫。
There's nothing that links him to the robberies.
还有那个小女招待在弗农 ？
And what about that little waitress in Vernon?
是啊 ， 我们给她看照片 ， 她说她没有认出他来。
Yeah, we showed her photos, and she said she didn't recognize him.
建议你带她相当的烦恼。
Pretty upset you took her tips as evidence.
她肯定很时髦。
She sure was sassy.
你证明 ， 旧的计时器 ？
You show that to that old timer?
是的。 他说 ， 他看上去像是你的从就餐者手中。
Yup. He said he didn't look like the fella from the diner.
他没认出 Tanner 的照片。
He didn't recognize Tanner's photo either.
是啊。 试图取得法院命令
Yeah. Tried to get a court order
在他的银行账户和牧场 ，
on his bank accounts and the ranch,
Da 。 Toby 没有记录。
da wouldn't do it. Toby's got no record.
他从来没有被逮捕。
He's never been arrested.
他只是在他出庭离婚案。
His only court appearance was at his divorce.
他没有达到这个标准 ， 马库斯。
He don't fit the bill, Marcus.
人们不要去抢劫银行。
People don't start out robbing banks.
他们毕业时 ， 希望能像他的弟弟混蛋。
They graduate to it like his asshole brother.
此外 ， 当我们到那里时 ，
Besides, when we was out there,
我们看到两个工作人员从雪佛龙
we saw two crews from chevron
压盖井和投放 pumpjacks 。
capping Wells and putting in pumpjacks.
工程师说那时候他们
Engineers out there said they're gonna pull
2000 桶 ， 请假一个月。
2,000 barrels a month off that place.
你只是试着说服法官
You just try convincing a judge
权某人
to issue warrants on somebody
清除 50000 美元不等 ， 每月从银行抢劫四万元
set to clear $50,000 a month for robbing $40,000 from the bank
家族信托管理。
that manages the family trust.
米德兰管理信托 ？
Midland manages the trust?
他们真是希望这东西。
You'd think they'd want this thing figured out.
我不认为银行不关心任何事
I don't think the bank cares about anything
但是 ， 就在其信任。
but keeping that trust right where it is.
地狱 ， 他们不那么合作的律师比托比。
Hell, they were less cooperative than Toby's attorney.
马库斯 ， 他并不是嫌疑犯 ， 你退休了
Marcus, he's not a suspect and you are retired.
哦 ， 我听到你。
Oh, I hear you.
你喜欢在桌子上吗 ？
You like the desk?
我不恨它。
I don't hate it.
嘿 ， 我看你 ， 马库斯。
Hey, I'll see you, Marcus.
知道我是谁吗 ？
Know who I am?
是我把你杀了哥哥。
I'm the man who killed your brother.
我知道。
I know.
我也知道你和你侵入。
I also know you're retired and you're trespassing.
哦 ， 现在你可以杀我
Oh, you could shoot me now
和是你的正当权利。
and be within your rights.
你的枪和所有 ， 多么方便。
You toting a gun and all, how convenient.
我想你也要去。
I figure you got one, too.
我能坐下吗 ？
Mind if I sit?
去吧。
Go ahead.
你要喝啤酒吗 ？
You want a beer?
当然。 我没有更多的责任。
Sure. I ain't on duty no more.
感谢。
Thanks.
很高兴在这个微风 ，
It's nice out here in this breeze, though,
现在 ， 它的冷却。
now that it's cooled down.
你是怎么做的 ？
How did you do it?
哦 ， 没关系。 我想出来的。
Oh, never mind. I'll figure that out in time.
为什么呢 ？ 你为什么这样做 ？
Why? Why did you do it?
我知道为什么你的哥哥 Tanner 、干的。
I know why your brother, Tanner, did it.
他抢劫银行 ， 因为他喜欢。
He robbed them banks because he liked it.
他射中我的合伙人 300 码远
He shot my partner 300 yards away
因为他很喜欢 ， 这让他感觉很好。
because he liked it, it made him feel good.
如果我没有把他的脑袋 ，
If I hadn't blown his shit for brains out,
一个新的卡车在摩托艇
there'd be a new truck out front with jet skis,
一切他能想到买。
and whatever else he could think to buy.
他买所有刚刚给他
He'd spend it all just to give him
更多的借口来窃取。
an excuse to steal some more.
但你不是。
But not you.
没有比这儿
There's nothing new around here,
他们除了 pumpjacks 。
except them pumpjacks.
每一个让你一个月
Each one of them making you a month
你和你弟弟偷了什么
what you and your brother stole
从所有 4 个有效组合。
from all four banks combined.
帮助我理解他 ， 然后。
Help me understand, then.
为什么 4 人死亡
Help me understand why four people died
所以 ， 钱你也偷不去 ，
so you could steal money that it don't seem you've spent,
它不需要你。
that it don't seem you need.
你有家人吗 ？
You got a family?
我的伙伴。 一个不容忽视的方面。
My partner had a family. A big one.
他们既没有 pumpjacks 在自己的后院。
They don't got no pumpjacks in their backyard.
我没有杀你的朋友。
I didn't kill your friend.
是的你没有。
Yes, you did.
通过设置这种运动的事物。
By setting this thing in motion.
你指望我相信这个计划对于你的兄弟吗 ？
You expect me to believe your dimwitted brother planned this?
哦 ， 不。 这很聪明 ， 这是你。
Oh, no. This was smart, this was you.
我可怜的我的整个生活。
I've been poor my whole life.
我的父母 ， 他们的父母在他们面前。
So were my parents, their parents before them.
这就像一种传染病
It's like a disease
传承性 ，
passing from generation to generation,
成为一种病 ， 就是这样。
becomes a sickness, that's what it is.
感染每个人你知道 ，
Infects every person you know,
但不是我的孩子们。
but not my boys.
以后不会了。
Not anymore.
这就是他们的了。
This is theirs now.
现在 ， 我没有杀任何人 ，
Now, I ain't never killed no one in my life,
但如果你要我开始与你 ，
but if you want me to start with you,
让我们赶快开始 ， 老男人。
let's get on with it, old man.
看看你是否能抓住手枪
See if you can grab that pistol
我在你这个门廊。
before I blast you off this porch.
你好。 怎么了?
Howdy. What's going on?
在猪的背部的花园。
The hogs are back in the garden.
猛兽撕裂了这个地方。
Feral hogs tearing up this place something fierce.
这是谁 ？
Who's this?
我的老朋友你丈夫。
I'm an old friend of your husband.
前夫。
Ex-husband.
我只是在造房子。
I'm just working on the house.
哦 ， 你不要住在这里吗 ？
Oh, you don't live here?
不 ， 不是我的。 是他们的。
No, it's not mine. It's theirs.
哦。
Oh.
我们为了我们的孩子 ， 对吗 ？
The things we do for our kids, huh?
好。..
Well...
我最好走了。
I best be going.
Ma 'am.
Ma'am.
我也是 ， 黛比。 我去洗漱 ，
Me too, Debbie. I'm gonna wash up,
是在 9 ： 00 前完成在明天。
be back around 9:00 tomorrow to finish the front.
绘画开始延伸 ，
Start painting the extension,
兰迪 ， 然后帮助他做作业
and then help Randy with his homework
当他从学校回来 ， 好吗 ？
when he gets back from school, okay?
好吧。
Okay.
嘿。
Hey.
我租房住的小房子。
I'm renting a little house in town.
如果你想停下来聊这个话题 ，
If you wanna stop by and finish this conversation,
欢迎你随时来玩。
you're welcome anytime.
哦 ， 我喜欢。
Oh, I'd like that.
我会再见到你。
I'll be seeing you.
是啊。 很快 ， 我希望。
Yeah. Soon, I hope.
我准备做这个。
I'm ready to be done with this.
你永远不会用它做什么。
You'll never be done with it no matter what.
它越缠着你 ， 儿子 ， 你的整个余生。
It's gonna haunt you, son, for the rest of your days.
但你不会孤独。 这样折磨我 ， 太。
But you won't be alone. It's gonna haunt me, too.
如果你顺道或许我就赐你平安。
If you stop by, maybe I'll give you peace.
也许。 也许我可以给你。
Maybe. Maybe I'll give it to you.